misterwhat.co.uk 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy | MisterWhat

Privacy Policy for the website  www.misterwhat.co.uk  administered by FABULABS S.p.A. The original version of this document is in Italian. In the event of any discrepancy between a translated version of this Agreement and the Italian version, the Italian version shall prevail.

##  1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) for  https://www.misterwhat.co.uk  (“Site”) describes who we are, what Personal Data we collect on or through the Site, how we obtain and use such information, what are the legal grounds for processing Personal Data, who has access to Personal Data, and what are the rights of the data subjects. Read this Policy carefully.

By visiting the Site, or by using the Service, you accept the privacy practices described in this Policy.

Data subjects have the right to object to the processing of their Personal Data carried out for our legitimate interests or for marketing purposes. Please refer to the section  “Rights of the data subjects”  for more information.

This Policy is incorporated into, and is subject to, the  MisterWhat  Terms of Use. Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Policy have the meaning given to them in the  MisterWhat  Terms of Use.

##  2\. About us

Fabulabs S.p.a.

Registered address: Galleria Polidoro 7 - 43121 - Parma - Italy

VAT N. IT02531310346

Email: 

Fabulabs S.p.a. is the “controller” of the personal data provided by Users and Visitors.  

##  3\. What personal data we collect and why

When Users or Visitors use the Service, they may provide, and we may collect Personal Data. Personal data is any information which identifies a person, whether directly (for example name and surname) or indirectly (for example, information about the use of our Services). Visitors and Users may provide us with Personal Data in various ways on the Service. For example, when they register for an Account, use the Service, request that we publish their business listing or send us customer service requests.

We collect the following Personal Data:

3.1 Information provided by Users and Visitors

  * Contact details provided by the User: Name, surname, email address and (optionally, only if the User voluntarily chooses to provide such information) postal address and telephone number. We may use this information to contact Users about their business listing on our directory, the content (for example reviews or photos) that they posted on the Site, and any other products and services that we may have agreed to provide to them;
  * Business details provided by the User: Company name, postal address, telephone number, details of the products and/or services offered by the business, at least one category indicating the main economic sector in which the company operates. This information is necessary to publish the business listing in our directory and to provide the best possible service. Users can also choose to provide additional information about the company (for example, opening hours and photos). If they choose to provide this optional information, we will process it for the purposes of publishing the business listing in our directory;
  * Correspondence: We collect any Personal Data that Visitors and Users may provide if they contact us by email, letter or telephone, in order to provide the best customer support.

3.2 “Automatically Collected" Information

We track the use of the Site through cookies and other similar technologies so that we can provide important features and functionality of the Service, monitor the use of the Site and provide a more personalized experience.

This “automatically collected" information may include IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites visited just before or just after using the Service, the pages or other content the Visitor or User views or interacts with on the Service, and the dates and times of the visit, access, or use of the Service. Please refer to our  Cookie Policy  for more information.

We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding a Visitor or User’s interaction with email messages, such as whether the Visitor or User opens, clicks on, or forwards a message. This information is collected on an aggregate level from all Users and Visitors.

3.3 Information provided by Integrated Services 

Visitors and Users may be given the option to access or register for the Service through the use of their username and passwords for certain services provided by third parties (each, an “Integrated Service”), such as through the use of their Google account, or otherwise have the option to authorize an Integrated Service to provide Personal Data or other information to us. By authorizing us to connect with an Integrated Service, Visitors and Users authorize us to access and store their name, email address, age range, gender, country, profile picture URL, and other information that the Integrated Service makes available to us, and to use and disclose it in accordance with this Policy. Visitors and Users should check their privacy settings on each Integrated Service to understand what information that Integrated Service makes available to us, and make changes as appropriate. Visitors and Users should review each Integrated Service’s terms of use and privacy policies carefully before using their services and connecting to our Service.

3.4 Information from Other Sources  

We may obtain information, including Personal Data, from third parties and sources other than the Service, such as our partners, advertisers, and Integrated Services. If we combine or associate information from other sources with Personal Data that we collect through the Service, we will treat the combined information as Personal Data in accordance with this Policy.

Information about companies, professionals, associations, when not provided directly by the company and/or professional, is gathered from various public sources, including company websites, professional registers, leaflets, etc. This information is processed for the purposes of publishing the company listings in our directory and providing the best possible service to Users and Visitors.   

##  4\. How we use the Personal Data we collect

We use the information that we collect in a variety of ways in providing the Service and operating our business, including the following:

4.1 Operations

We use Personal Data to:

  * operate, maintain, enhance and provide all features of the Site, and to provide the services and information that Visitors and Users request;
  * publish the business listing on our directory and provide the Services;
  * publish the reviews and photos that Users ask us to publish;
  * confirm the identity and the information that Visitors and Users have provided. We need to confirm identity for security reasons and to safeguard the data in our directory (for example when we process a request to modify a business listing);
  * remove a business listing, if a User or Visitor tells us to (see the “How to contact us” section).

4.2 Improvements to the Service

We use the information to:

  * understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our Visitors and Users;
  * improve the Service, and develop new products, services, features, and functionality.

Should this purpose require  MisterWhat  to process Personal Data, then the data will only be used in anonymized or aggregated form.

4.3 Cookies and tracking technologies

We use automatically collected information and other information collected on the Service through cookies and similar technologies to:

  * personalize our Service, such as remembering a User’s or Visitor’s information so that the User or Visitor will not have to re-enter it during a visit or on subsequent visits;
  * provide personalized advertisements, content, and information;
  * monitor and analyze the effectiveness of our marketing activities; 
  * monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed.

Please read our  Cookie Policy  for more information.

We also may use tracking technologies to collect information regarding how Visitors or Users interact with the email messages we send, to get information like the time and day they opened our emails and the type of device they used to open them. We use this information to analyze the effectiveness of our email communication in order to improve it and to provide a better and more personalized service.

4.4 Analytics

We use Google Analytics to measure and evaluate access to and traffic on the Public Area of the Site, and create navigation reports for our Site administrators. Google operates independently from us and has its own privacy policy, which we strongly suggest Visitors and Users to review. Google may use the information collected through Google Analytics to evaluate Users' and Visitors’ activity on our Site. For more information, see  [Google Analytics Privacy and Data Sharing](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245).

We take measures to protect the technical information collected by our use of Google Analytics. The data collected will only be used on a need to know basis to resolve technical issues, administer the Site and identify visitor preferences; but in this case, the data will be in non-identifiable form. We do not use any of this information to identify Visitors or Users.

4.5 Communications

We use Personal Data to:

  * communicate with Visitors and Users about our products and services, for example to let them know about major changes to our products or services, to the Terms of Use or to this Privacy Policy;
  * respond to comments and questions, provide support to Users and Visitors, and improve our customer service;
  * contact Users with updates on promotions and events, relating to products and services offered by us and by third parties we work with. Users have the ability to opt-out of receiving any promotional communications by managing the notification preferences in their account.

4.6 Enquiries, complaints and disputes

We use Personal Information to help us respond to any enquiries or complaints, or deal with any disputes which may arise while we provide our products and services, in the most effective way.

4.7 Fraud prevention and compliance with legal obligations

Under certain circumstances, we use Personal Data to the extent required in order to enable us to comply with our legal obligations, for example to investigate, detect and prevent fraud. This may require us to provide Personal Data to law enforcement agencies or officials, if they request it.

4.8 Internal training  

We may use Personal Data for internal training purposes, so that our staff has the skills needed to provide our Visitors and Users with the best possible experience. For example, if a User or Visitor contacts us by email, we may use their email for training purposes to improve our customer support.

4.9 Market research and analysis

We may use Personal Data to better understand the needs of our Users. We may also invite some Users to take part in surveys or market research. If a User accepts our invitation, we will use the feedback to improve our products and services.

4.10 Internal records and accuracy

Like any company, we process Personal Data to administer and maintain our internal records. For example, we process Personal Data to verify that the information we have about a User is accurate.

##  5\. Legal grounds for processing Personal Data

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) lists several legal grounds for the lawful processing of Personal Data, and requires us to only process Personal Data if we satisfy one or more legal grounds. 

We rely on a number of different legal grounds for the processing of Personal Data:

The data subject has given consent to the processing of his or her personal data for one or more specific purposes

In some cases we process Personal Data after obtaining a User’s or Visitor’s consent to do so for the purposes of:

  * sending marketing communications about our products and services;
  * sending marketing communications regarding products and services offered by third parties with whom we collaborate;
  * conducting market analysis and research.

Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party

It is necessary for us to  process Personal Data, and information about the business that a User represents, for the performance of the contract between us and Visitor/User, and to provide the Service.

Data processing is necessary to:

  * publish a business listing in our directory ;

  * publish the reviews and photos that a User asks us to publish ;

  * send communications about the products and services we provide, for example to inform Visitors and Users of major changes to these products or services, the Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy;
  * confirm a User or Visitor’s identity, and verify the information they provide to us;
  * provide and improve customer support.

If a Visitor or User chooses not to give some or all the aforementioned information, this may affect our ability to provide our products and services to them.

Processing is necessary for compliance with our legal obligations

Under certain circumstances, we may process Personal Data to comply with our legal obligations, for example to investigate, detect and prevent fraud.

Processing is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests

To consider this as lawful basis for processing, a business must have legitimate interests which are not overridden by individuals' interests, rights or freedoms.

Collecting and processing Personal Data is necessary for our legitimate business interests, which are:

  * to better understand our Users and Visitors so we can improve our products and services;
  * to improve and develop our Site to enhance the customer experience;
  * to provide important features and functionality on our Site, monitor its usage and provide a more personalized experience;
  * to provide Visitors and Users with products and services that are as useful as possible, for example to inform them of offers that may be of interest to their business;
  * to train our staff so that they can offer the best customer support;
  * to respond to any enquiries or complaints, or handle any disputes that might arise while we provide our products and services, in the most effective way;
  * to manage our business effectively, to comply with our legal obligations, and to be able to exercise, or defend against, legal claims.

We may process Personal Data based on our legitimate interests  except where such interests are overridden by the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject.

We have assessed these aspects carefully and, on balance, we believe that our interests described above are balanced with the fundamental interests, rights or freedoms of  the data subjects.

Where we think there is a risk that one of the fundamental interests or freedoms of a Visitor or User may be compromised, we will not process their data unless there is another lawful legal basis for doing so (if we have obtained their consent to the processing or to comply with our legal obligations or if processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with them).

##  6\. Who we share Personal Data with

Except as described in this Policy, we will not intentionally disclose the Personal Data that we collect or store on the Service to third parties without the consent of the applicable Visitor or User. We may disclose information to third parties if a Visitor or User consent to us doing so, as well as in the following circumstances:

6.1 Unrestricted Information

Any information that a User voluntarily chooses to include in a Public Area of the Service, such as a public profile page or business listing, will be available to any Visitor or User who has access to that content.

6.2 Service Providers

We may provide Personal Data to our service providers, who provide us with certain services and act as "processors" of Personal Data on our behalf. These third parties may have access to, or process Personal Data as part of providing those services for us. We limit the information provided to these service providers to that which is reasonably necessary for them to perform their functions.

6.3  Law Enforcement

We may disclose Personal Data:

  * if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with applicable laws, in response to a facially valid court order, judicial or other government subpoena or warrant, or to otherwise cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental agencies;
  * to protect the security or integrity of the Service;
  * to protect our property or other legal rights, enforce our contracts, or protect the rights, property, or safety of others; 
  * to protect ourselves or others from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or activity;
  * to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations.

6.4 Change of Ownership

Information about Users and Visitors, including Personal Data, may be disclosed and otherwise transferred to an acquirer, successor or assignee as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of assets, or similar transaction, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which information is transferred to one or more third parties as one of our business assets and only if the recipient of the Personal Data commits to a Privacy Policy that has terms substantially consistent with this Privacy Policy.

In some cases, the Personal Data we collect for the above purposes may be transferred outside the European Economic Area (EEA), and such destinations may not have laws protecting Personal Data to the same extent as in the European Economic Area. Data protection law requires us to ensure that where we or our "processors" transfer Personal Data outside the European Economic Area, it is processed securely and protected from unauthorized access, loss, destruction, unlawful processing, and any type of processing that is not consistent with the purposes outlined in this Policy.

We will comply with GDPR requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of personal information outside of the European Economic Area (EEA).

The table below lists the third parties to whom we currently disclose Personal Data. The table also explains how these organizations use Personal Data, if they are our "processors" (they process the data on our behalf, and only in line with our instructions), or if they are "controllers" (they use Personal Data for their own purposes, after receiving them). The table indicates if the treatment is performed outside the EEA, and the safeguards that are used to protect Personal Data if this is the case.

This information may be updated periodically.

Recipient

| 

Why we share Personal Data

| 

Where Personal Data is processed

| 

Safeguards that are used to protect Personal Data outside the EEA  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Service providers acting as “Processors”  
  
OVH

| 

OVH hosts our data.

| 

France

| 

N/D – processing is taking place within the EEA.  
  
SendGrid

| 

Provides email delivery services.

| 

SendGrid uses data centers all over the world to provide its services.

| 

SendGrid's GDPR Data Processing Addendum, signed between Sendgrid and Fabulabs S.p.a., states that:

“To the extent that SendGrid processes (or causes to be processed) any Personal Data originating from the EEA in a country that has not been designated by the European Commission as providing an adequate level of protection for Personal Data, the Personal Data shall be deemed to have adequate protection (within the meaning of EU Data Protection Legislation) by virtue of SendGrid's self-certification to the Privacy Shield. SendGrid shall agree to apply the Privacy Shield Principles when processing (or causing to be processed) any EEA or Swiss Personal Data under this Agreement.” The contract also lists a number of additional security measures and GDPR obligations that Sendgrid is subject to under the Agreement.    
  
Google

| 

Monitoring and aggregate analysis of website traffic through  Google Analytics.

| 

EEA, US

| 

Please refer to  <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

for more information on how Google uses information from sites or apps that use its services  

Google is certified under the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks, and is committed to GDPR compliance across its services.

For more information:

<https://cloud.google.com/security/gdpr/>  
  
Other organizations we share Personal Data with, acting as "Controllers”  
  
Google

| 

Traffic monetization through targeted online advertising (Google AdSense).

| 

EEA, US

| 

See “Google” above”  
  
As a consequence of our use of Google products, some of the ad technology providers listed below may receive your Personal Data. Ad technology providers (including Google and other ad networks and vendors) use data about users, for example, for the purposes of ads personalization and measurement. These ad technology providers have provided Google with information about their compliance with the GDPR. 

##  7\. Data Retention

We only retain the Personal Data for a limited period of time as long as we need it to fulfill the purposes for which we have initially collected it, unless otherwise required by law.

The retention period may vary depending on the type of data. To determine retention periods, we consider a variety of factors, such as:

  * legal obligations to retain data for a certain period of time, in accordance with the law;
  * statute of limitations under applicable law;
  * guidelines issued by relevant data protection authorities;
  * the presence of actual or potential disputes.

We securely delete Personal Data from our systems when they are no longer needed.

##  8\. Rights of the data subject

The GDPR provides the following rights for individuals:

1\. Right to be informed

Data subjects have the right to receive concise, transparent, intelligible, easily accessible information on how we use their Personal Data. This is why we provide the information contained in this Privacy Policy.

2\. Right of access

Data subjects have the right to obtain:

  * confirmation that we are processing their Personal Data;
  * a copy of their Personal Data;
  * other information similar to that provided in this Privacy Policy.

3\. Right to rectification

Data subjects have the right to have inaccurate Personal Data rectified, or completed if it is incomplete.

4\. Right to erasure ("right to be forgotten")

Data subjects have the right to request the deletion or removal of their Personal Data, if:

  * the personal data is no longer necessary for the purpose which we originally collected or processed it for;
  * they withdraw their consent;
  * they object to the processing of their Personal Data;
  * we have processed the Personal Data unlawfully;
  * we have to delete the data to comply with a legal obligation;
  * data was collected from children.

This is not a general right to erasure; there are exceptions.

5\. Right to restrict processing

In certain circumstances, data subjects have the right to restrict the processing of their Personal Data. When processing is restricted, we are permitted to store the Personal Data, but not use it.

6\. Right to data portability

Data subjects have the right to receive their Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format.

7\. Right to object

Data subjects have the right to object to the processing of their Personal Data in certain circumstances (when data is being used for direct marketing, or when processing is based upon our legitimate interests).

8\. Right to withdraw consent to processing

If data subjects have given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data for a particular purpose (for example, direct marketing), they have the right to withdraw their consent at any time.

9\. Minors and children’s privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. Our Service is not directed to children under the age of 16, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 16 without obtaining parental consent. If you are under 16 years of age, then please do not use or access the Service at any time or in any manner. If we learn that Personal Data has been collected on the Service from persons under 16 years of age and without verifiable parental consent, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under 16 years of age has obtained an Account on the Service, then you may alert us (see ‘How to contact us’ below’) and request that we delete that child’s Personal Data from our systems.

##  10\. Data Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect Personal Data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Data in our possession. This includes, for example, firewalls, password protection and other access and authentication controls. We use SSL technology to encrypt data during transmission through public internet.

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that Visitors and Users transmit to us or that is stored on the Service, and Visitors and Users use the Site at their own risk. We also cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If a User or Visitor believes that their Personal Data has been compromised, they should contact us as set forth in the “How to contact us” section.

If we learn of a security systems breach, we will inform Visitors and Users and the authorities of the occurrence of the breach in accordance with applicable law.

##  11\.  How to contact us

Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Policy, Personal Data, or if you would like to exercise your data protection rights, or if you have any concerns or complaints about this Policy or your Personal Data, by sending an email to:    

##  12\.  Links to other websites

The Site contains features or links to websites and services provided by third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those other websites. Any information that Visitors and Users provide on third-party sites or services is provided directly to the operators of such services and is subject to those operators’ policies, if any, governing privacy and security, even if accessed through the Service. the contents and for the privacy practices of such third party websites, and Visitors and Users use such websites is at their own risk. We encourage our Visitors and Users to learn about third parties’ privacy and security policies before providing them with information.

##  13\.  Changes and updates to this Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 15 May 2018.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time so Visitors and Users may wish to revisit this page each time they provide Personal Data to us. Continued use of the Service by Visitors and Users after the revised Policy has become effective indicates that they have read, understood and agreed to the current version of the Policy.

This Cookie Policy explains what cookies are, the different types of cookies used on the Site, and how you can change or delete them. We hope that this policy helps you understand our use of cookies. 

## What are Cookies?

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or mobile device and hold data relating to a specific website. Cookies are placed on the User/Visitor's computer or mobile device by that website and accessed each time a User/Visitor browses the site. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work in a better, more efficient way, to make websites easier to use, to support the provision of relevant functionalities to the User/Visitor. Cookies enable websites to recognise you and remember important information that will make your use of a website more convenient, for example by remembering your preferences. We primarily use cookies to collect data that help us improve our website by knowing which parts of the site are being visited, how Users/Visitors are accessing each page and what items on each page they prefer to click on. The types of information typically collected by cookies include information relating to your use of the Site, your browser type, your device's IP address, how you arrived on the Site etc.   
Cookies come in different categories. By using this Site you accept our use of cookies. If you wish to restrict or block web browser cookies which are set on your device, You do this through your browser settings at any time. The Help function within your browser should tell you how. For further information on how to change your browser settings and on cookies in general, you may visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of desktop browsers. Please note that preventing the use of cookies is likely to impact the performance and functionality of this Site, or prevent you from using certain services provided by this Site. If you choose to prevent the use of cookies, we cannot guarantee that all services and functionalities provided by this Site will perform or work correctly during your visit. 

## Types of Cookies used

Further information about the types of cookies that are used on this Site can be found below. 

**Essential Cookies**   
These cookies are strictly necessary to the Site in order to enable you to navigate through the websites and to use their features. No information about your browsing habits is gathered by these cookies. Without these essential and absolutely necessary cookies, certain aspects of the Site would not work. 

**Analytics Cookies**   
Analytics cookies collect information about how Users/Visitors interact with the Site, and enable us to improve the way the website works, provide better products and services and identify any areas of the Site that may need maintenance.   
For example, analytics cookies show us which are the most frequently visited pages on the Site, help us record any difficulties you have with the navigation, show us where error messages are delivered and whether advertising is effective or not. This allows us to see the main patterns of usage on the Site. Some of the analytics cookies we use may be operated by trusted third parties. Accepting analytics cookies is a condition of using the Site and by continuing to use the Site, you agree we can place analytics cookies on your device.   
These cookies are just used for statistics, they don't collect information that identifies individuals and we can't identify you personally through the use of these cookies. All information provided by these cookies is anonymous. 

**Functional Cookies**   
We use functional cookies to remember how you use the Site and the choices you make. For example, functional cookies allow this Site to remember your user name, log in details, and any customisations you make to the Site during your visit. We can't identify you personally through the use of these cookies, nor do these cookies track your browsing habits, but they do help us serve you with ads. 

**Advertising or targeting cookies**   
Targeting or advertising cookies collect information about your browsing behaviour and habits in order to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests and help measure the effectiveness of advertising on the Site.   
We use third party cookies to make advertising relevant to the content/pages you are visiting and to your interests. The Site uses targeting or advertising cookies to provide Google and other advertising partners and advertising networks with information on your visit so that they can present you with relevant advertising that you may find interesting; we link to social networking websites like Facebook, Twitter who may then use information about your visit to target advertising to you on other properties. 

**Other Cookies**   
Some of the cookies on the Site are operated by third parties, such as Google, Facebook and Twitter. We do not control these third parties or their use of cookies, and it is not possible for us to manage these cookies. Please visit the websites of those third parties for details on how they use cookies. 

## How can I reject or opt out of receiving cookies?

When you first visited this website you will have been shown a message bar drawing your attention to the fact that this website uses cookies and inviting you to review this cookie policy and manage your cookie preferences. If you do not set your preferences despite this prompt a cookie preference cookie will be dropped confirming that you consent to us using the cookies detailed in this cookie policy, this cookie preference cookie will last for no more than 5 years.   
Please note that we can't always control third party cookies stored on your machine from our website and setting your cookie preferences with us will not stop those third party cookies from being stored on your machine, you must manage these cookies directly with the relevant third party, please see our "How to control cookies" section below for more information.   
If you have previously consented to us storing cookies on your machine but then change your mind, you can do the following: 

  * delete the cookies from your browser. Most browsers also allow you to prevent all or some cookies being stored on your machine in the future. For more information on how to delete or disable cookies from your browser please use the "help" function within your browser or alternatively visit www.allaboutcookies.org . By deleting our cookie preference cookie the next time you visit this website the cookie message bar will appear again inviting you to again reconsider your preferences.
  * if you only want to reject some or all of the third party cookies you will need to visit the relevant third party's website directly to manage cookies stored on your machine by them. Please see our "How to control cookies" section below.

Please be aware that disabling cookies may impact the functionality of this website. 

## How to control cookies

You are not obliged to accept cookies and may refuse to accept cookies from the Site at any time by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse cookies. Further information about the procedure to follow in order to disable cookies can be found on your Internet browser provider's website via your help screen. Please be aware that if cookies are disabled, not all functionalities of the Site may function or operate as intended.   
You may wish to refer to the resources listed below:   
\- Terminology and definitions - For more information see [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)   
\- To learn more about how Google uses data when you use its partners' sites or apps, please visit <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites>   
\- For further information about Google advertising cookies and how to opt out, please see [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/)   
\- For further information about Google Analytics, including how to opt out, please see <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245> and <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>   
\- For further information about Facebook's privacy policy, advertising practices, and for information on how to prevent being tracked for advertising purposes by Facebook, please see <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy> \- <https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies>   
If you would like to learn more about advertising networks, affiliate programmes and how cookies are used for advertising purposes, please see [www.youronlinechoices.com/uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk). This is a useful portal run by IAB (Internet Advertising Bureau), provides all the information about online advertising and the choices available to you. To prevent being tracked by advertising networks and other organisations please see <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>.
